{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"deter","osnova2":"ent","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"emper","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eparac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ungla","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"ho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pan","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"benik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"kra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"novoro","osnova2":"enče","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"oru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poga","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poro","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"strojovo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tvr","osnova2":"ava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"uspore","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
